{
    "id": "349f9ca4127e4fbfb6e607c4ed8043b0",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I would rather you ………………….. home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I decided to write rather than ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "phone",
                "phoning",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish you …………………. that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't do",
                "hadn't done"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a psychologist – or …………………, a psychoanalyst",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "better",
                "rather",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The reason …………………. I came here was to be with my family.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "why",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I cut …………………. shaving this morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "myself"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s have a party, …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "let we",
                "shall we",
                "could we"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She wondered why ………………… wearing a coat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wasn't he",
                "he wasn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The cake ……………….. wonderful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tastes",
                "is tasting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. you are getting married.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hear",
                "am hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}